<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RKU Guide</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Ayurvedic-->
    <string name="aboutAyurvedic">➠ Life is getting faster and faster day by day so as the rate of
        increment in unpredictable diseases around human beings. The number of remediless
        diseases is increasing with a higher rate. But there is a path through which these
        incurable diseases can be cured. In between the busy lifestyles, there exists a way
        through which the life, health, mind, body and heart remain free from unwanted damage,
        incurable diseases.
        \n\n➠ RK University knows the value of this Traditional Indian System of Medicine
        (Ayurveda) which is precious thing for mankind. Modern techniques of learning,
        practical knowledge for every single topic, laboratories with high quality equipments
        and well qualified faculties, give the students a perfect platform to build their
        career as BAMS (Bachelor of Ayurvedic Medicine And Surgery) and help them becoming a
        successful professional in Ayurveda sector. Several numbers of medical camps,
        seminars, health awareness programs, interaction with globally known personalities
        of Ayurveda and continuous practical knowledge provided by Ayurvedic College
        and Hospital, give the right platform to the students to learn and develop
        themselves in Ayurveda field. Ayurvedic College and Hospital also has one of the
        most modern libraries in Gujarat region which provides the best resources of
        Ayurveda to the students.
    </string>
    <string name="ayurvedicCourse">1. Bachelor Of Ayurvedic Medicine And Surgery</string>


    <!-- TODO: Details Of BestPlace-->
    <string name="aboutAnalgadh">➠ This is an off beat location, a beautiful and peaceful attraction and one of
                the top places near Rajkot. Analgadh hill is a popular weekend getaway and an escape
                from the chaos of the city.  You can capture the sweeping views of the picture-perfect
                surroundings. You can also find an ancient Hindu temple where a number of devotees
                flock every year.
                \n\n➠ You can also explore top adventure activities including hiking, trekking and cycling
                besides engaging yourself in photography to capture the stunning greenery.
                \n\n➠ Location: Analgadh, Gujarat
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Family and Kids
                \n➠ Opening hours: Anytime
    </string>

    <string name="aboutIshwariya">➠ Located in the city, Ishwariya Park is a popular place inaugurated
                in the year 2008. It is a 77 acre attraction that attracts a lot of tourists who
                can enjoy boating, picnic and multiple outdoor games. Best visited during autumn
                or spring season, if you are looking for a place to relax, then this is built for
                you! There is a water fountain, which is one of the major attraction inside the park.
                \n\n➠ Location: Rajkot, Gujarat 360006
                \n➠ Entry Fees: INR 10 for kids, INR 20 for adults
                \n➠ Ideal for: Picnic
                \n➠ Opening hours: 1 pm to 8 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutPraduman">➠ Located near Lalpari lake in Rajkot, this park is one of the famous places 
                in Rajkot. The park is spread across an area of 137 acres and offers many species 
                of animals and plants. If you are visiting Rajkot with your family, then you must 
                visit this place for a soul-satisfying experience.
                \n\n➠ Location: Pradhyuman Park, Rajkot, Gujarat 360003
                \n➠ Entry Fees: INR 10 for adults, INR 5 for children
                \n➠ Ideal for: Family outing
                \n➠ Opening hours: 9 am to 6 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutLalPari">➠ A few kilometres from Rajkot city is Lal Pari Lake, another picturesque
                locale that’s one of the most terrific picnic spots in Gujarat. It’s among the more
                popular tourist places near Rajkot as like Aji Dam, it attracts various migratory
                birds who put on quite a show.
                \n\n➠ Location: Navagam, Rajkot, Gujarat 360003
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Leisure
                \n➠ Opening Hours: 9 am to 6 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutNyari">➠ When you want to take a break from museums, we recommend heading to Nyari Dam,
                a scenic Rajkot place to visit that’s perfect for a picnic. It’s located five
                kilometres from Rajkot and although frequented by tourists and locals, it still
                retains a peaceful ambience. The views are lovely and if you stay till evening you
                can catch a beautiful sunset. It is one of the most romantic tourist places in Rajkot
                for couples. In fact, you can find one of the best hotels in Gujarat here.
                \n\n➠ Location: Nyari Dam Rd, Rajkot, Gujarat  360005
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Leisure
                \n➠ Opening Hours: 24 hours
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of BestFood-->
    <string name="aboutGathiya">➠ Ganthiya is a special dish of Gujarat. It makes the best combination
        with sweet chutney and chilly. It is the best side dish with tea or coffee during breakfast
        or snack time. It is delicious and healthy.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutDabeli">➠ Dabeli is the most loved snack item of all the people all over 
        the country. Dabeli marks its origin from Gujarat. It is a delicacy which is like Vada pav 
        of Maharashtra, but the main difference is that instead of Vada, they put mashed potato, 
        groundnut, spices, pomegranates, dates, and tamarind. It is tasty and healthy too.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutGhu">➠ Ghughra is a sweet dish from Gujarat which is loved by all 
        the Gujarati’s. People make this dish during festivals and other occasions. It has some
        sweet stuffing coated with the dough. It is cut in the shape of half moon and is baked. 
        It is delicious and healthy too.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutDal">➠ Dal Pakwan is one of the most famous Sindhi breakfast recipe. 
        Dal pakwan is basically chana dal served with pakwan (crisp fried Indian bread).
    </string>

    <string name="aboutBhungada">➠ Bhungara Bateta  is a mad street food of Rajkot.
        It is spicy with red gravy. Additionally, it contains a mild sweet flavour.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Hostel-->
    <string name="aboutBoysHostel">The hostels are well maintained. The hostel building is having
                construction and maintenance in order to accommodate more people and provide new
                facilities. We have 3 seater rooms with attached washrooms, washing machines on
                each floor, badminton court, table tennis.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutGirlsHostel">Hostels are good. We have 4 room mate in single room.
        One table is provided in room. One bed is also provided. Two shelfs are provided for putting
        some books. One almira is also provided.
    </string>
    <string name="hostelRules">➠ A student must abide by the Hostel Policy, Rules and Code od Conduct at the
                time of admission to the hostel.\n\n
                ➠ Room allocation is done by the warden based on the choice of the student or/end
                availability in 04/06/07 sharing rooms.\n\n
                ➠ Transfer of room is to be done with official process and authorized by the worden based
                on availability\n\n
                ➠ All the furniture will be provided by the hostel in-charge. The student will incur if any
                item is found damaged or missing from their room due to careless/negligent handling.\n\n
                ➠ Electric appliances shall not be permitted in the room, defiance of which shall enable
                the worden/Campus Administrator to confiscate the gadget forthwith (e.g. iron, induction stove.)\n\n
                ➠ Campus administration like warden/security may come and check your room at any time.\n\n
                ➠ Vehicles are not allowed inside the hostel premises for the hosteler. If student want
                to keep the vehicle, need to park at general parking area which is outside of the campus.\n\n
                ➠ Hostel authorities can terminate the occupancy in case of willful disobedience or
                defiance of authority . non - observance of hostel rules , causing damage to person
                or property or anti - social , anti - national or undesirable activities as Ragging ,
                Gambling , Alcohol / Drugs / Smoking , Misuse of Internet and Online social media ,
                Firearms , Pets , cooking inside the room , political and communal activities etc.\n\n
                ➠ During the vacation student need to keep all the things into the locker.\n\n
                ➠ Students need to mark his / her signature on the attendance muster between
                08:00 pm to 9:30 pm ( Based on the allocated time by warden ) in the presence of warden.\n\n
                ➠ Student can go outside with permission of warden ( Gate Pass ) once in a week.
                In such case student need to return at campus on or before 07:00 pm.\n\n
                ➠ The student is permitted to go outstation for participating in various competitions
                only after submitting proof and application along with parent\'s consent to the
                warden and getting permission of the warden.\n\n
                ➠ Students need to return from outstation before 09:00 pm ( Based on the given
                time by warden ) , after which gates will be closed . ( In case of late arrival ,
                student need to inform to warden and take prior permission ).\n\n
                ➠ Visitors / Parents are allowed to visit a student only in the visitor\'s lobby on
                the service floor between 9:00 am to 6:00 pm . Parents are not allowed to visit room.\n\n
                ➠ Strict silence shall be observed in hostel from 12.00 midnight to 6.00 pm.
                Care shall be always taken to ensure that music / loud talking is not audible
                outside the room . Any manner of festivities and noise making / celebrations ,
                which may cause disturbance to other inmates in the hostel premises , will not
                be allowed.\n\n
                ➠ Strict silence shall be observed in hostel from 12.00 midnight to 6.00 pm.
                Care shall be always taken to ensure that music / loud talking is not audible
                outside the room . Any manner of festivities and noise making / celebrations ,
                which may cause disturbance to other inmates in the hostel premises , will
                not be allowed.\n\n
                ➠ The student shall keep their rooms , veranda , and surrounding areas tidy ,
                neat , and clean always and shall not throw anything including trash , in such
                places or any premises in the hostel , except in the dustbin or the place
                specifically provided for the said purpose.\n\n
                ➠ The student shall always treat the hostel staff , security , and housekeeping
                staff of the hostel with due courtesy . Service of the housekeeping staff shall
                not be utilized for private or personal work . No tips in cash or kind should
                be given to the staff of the hostel.\n\n
                ➠ In case of medical emergency , student should contact to warden.\n\n
                ➠ All the rights are reserved by the management.
    </string>

</resources>