<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RKU Guide</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Ayurvedic-->
    <string name="aboutAyurvedic">Life is getting faster and faster day by day so as the rate of
        increment in unpredictable diseases around human beings. The number of remediless
        diseases is increasing with a higher rate. But there is a path through which these
        incurable diseases can be cured. In between the busy lifestyles, there exists a way
        through which the life, health, mind, body and heart remain free from unwanted damage,
        incurable diseases.
    </string>
    <string name="ayurvedicCourse">1. Bachelor Of Ayurvedic Medicine And Surgery</string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Agriculture-->
    <string name="aboutAgriculture">It is a 4 year long Undergraduate Bachelor Degree programme.
        B. Sc. (Hons.) Agriculture programme consists of subjects such as Agronomy, Agricultural
        Meteorology, Soil Science, Genetics and Plant Breeding, Seed Science, Plant Pathology,
        Agriculture Entomology, Horticulture, Extension Education, Agricultural Economics,
        Agriculture Engineering, Agricultural Statistics, Animal and Poultry Management, Plant
        Biotechnology etc- The main aim of this programme is to train students to improve the
        agriculture sector in India, pave the way for future developments through research
        activities and transfer that research to farmers for increase production and sustainability.
        \nThis program aims at combining concepts of RESEARCH, EDUCATION and EXTENSION to boost
        the agricultural sector.
    </string>
    <string name="agricultureCourse">1. Bachelor Of Agriculture Science</string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Physio-->
    <string name="aboutPhysio">The institute established in 2005, with broad mission and vision to
                develop excellence in health care profession. The institute was well known as a
                RK College of Physiotherapy, RK Group of Colleges, Rajkot affiliated to Saurashtra
                University, Rajkot and now famous as School of Physiotherapy, affiliated to
                RK University, Rajkot.The school is also recognized by the Indian Association of
                Physiotherapists (IAP), the IAP is a member organization of the World Confederation
                of Physical Therapy (WCPT). Well qualified faculties, advance technology in laboratories
                and large exposure to clinical setups remains first priority for the school.
    </string>
    <string name="physioCourse">1. BPT\n    (Bachelor of Physiotherapy)\n\n
                2. MPT\n    (Master of Physiotherapy)
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of SOE-->
    <string name="aboutSOE">School of Engineering is one of the best degree engineering colleges
                in Gujarat state. School of Engineering is AICTE approved and located in a
                40 acre of lush-green campus on Rajkot-Bhavnagar highway at Rajkot, Gujarat. Earlier
                known as RK College of Engineering and Technology, the school envisage a world-class
                education system that assures quality and empowers the students to be the global 
                leaders of tomorrow. The school strives to bring excellence in the teaching-learning 
                process through continuous evaluation and training in educational pedagogy.
    </string>
    <string name="more">READ MORE</string>
    <string name="soeCourse">1. Mechanical Engineering\n    Diploma\n\n
                2. Civil Engineering\n    Diploma\n\n
                3. Computer Engineering\n    Diploma\n\n
                4. Electrical Engineering\n    Diploma\n\n
                5. Computer Engineering\n    Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)\n\n
                6. Civil Engineering\n    Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)\n\n
                7. Electrical Engineering\n    Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)\n\n
                8. Information Technology\n    Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)\n\n
                9. Mechanical Engineering\n      Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech)\n\n
                10. Computer Engineering\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                11. Construction Technology\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                12. Humanities And Applied Science\n\n
                13. Electrical Power System\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                14. Machine Design\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                15. Structural Engineering\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                16. Thermal Sciences\n      Master of Technology (M.Tech)\n\n
                17. BCA\n      Bachelor of Computer Applications\n\n
                18. MCA\n      Master of Computer Applications
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of SOM-->
    <string name="aboutSOM">School of Management started its journey offering MBA
                program in the year 2005 as RK College of Business Management.
                Since becoming a university in the year 2011, now the institution is known as
                School of Management, a constituent school of RK University, Rajkot.
    </string>
    <string name="somCourse">1. BBA\n    (Bachelor of Business Administration)\n\n
                2. B.Voc\n    (Bachelor of Vocational Studies)\n\n
                3. MBA\n    (Master of Business Administration)
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of SOP-->
    <string name="aboutSOP">School of Pharmacy is engaged in imparting education of Bachelors,
                Masters and Doctorate degrees in Pharmacy. The school is a part of campus of
                RK University and houses 20 laboratories, 4 class rooms, auditorium, library with
                Wi-Fi network, learning resource centre, medicinal garden, museum, seminar hall,
                central instrumentation room, animal house and administrative area.
                The building is an architectural splendor with ultramodern amenities, specifically
                designed to suit the requirements of Pharmacy education.
    </string>
    <string name="sopCourse">1. Pharm D.\n     (Doctor Of Pharmacy)\n\n
                2. B.Pharm\n     (Bachelor Of Pharmacy)\n\n
                3. M.Pharm\n     (Master Of Pharmacy)
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of SOS-->
    <string name="aboutSOS">RK University, formerly the RK Group of Colleges, is a leading
                University offering variety of courses ranging from Diploma studies to
                Doctorate research.\n\n
                Since its inception in the year of 2005, the RK group of Colleges has made a
                constant endeavour to provide quality education and a platform for overall development
                to its students. The journey from Group of Colleges to A State-Private University Status has
                been a daunting task with challenges and opportunities. It’s a collective and constant
                effort of RK family that we have scaled this height.
    </string>
    <string name="sosCourse">1. Diploma In Medical Laboratory Technology\n\n
                2. B.Sc Chemistry\n    (Bachelor Of Science)\n\n
                3. B.Sc Microbiology\n    (Bachelor Of Science)\n\n
                4. B.Sc Physics\n    (Bachelor Of Science)\n\n
                5. B.Sc Mathematics\n    (Bachelor Of Science)\n\n
                6. M.Sc Organic Chemistry\n    (Master Of Science)\n\n
                7. M.Sc Analytical Chemistry\n    (Master Of Science)\n\n
                8. M.Sc Microbiology\n    (Master Of Science)\n\n
                9. M.Sc Physics\n    (Master Of Science)
    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Details Of BestPlace-->
    <string name="aboutAnalgadh">➠ This is an off beat location, a beautiful and peaceful attraction and one of
                the top places near Rajkot. Analgadh hill is a popular weekend getaway and an escape
                from the chaos of the city.  You can capture the sweeping views of the picture-perfect
                surroundings. You can also find an ancient Hindu temple where a number of devotees
                flock every year.
                \n\n➠ You can also explore top adventure activities including hiking, trekking and cycling
                besides engaging yourself in photography to capture the stunning greenery.
                \n\n➠ Location: Analgadh, Gujarat
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Family and Kids
                \n➠ Opening hours: Anytime
    </string>

    <string name="aboutIshwariya">➠ Located in the city, Ishwariya Park is a popular place inaugurated
                in the year 2008. It is a 77 acre attraction that attracts a lot of tourists who
                can enjoy boating, picnic and multiple outdoor games. Best visited during autumn
                or spring season, if you are looking for a place to relax, then this is built for
                you! There is a water fountain, which is one of the major attraction inside the park.
                \n\n➠ Location: Rajkot, Gujarat 360006
                \n➠ Entry Fees: INR 10 for kids, INR 20 for adults
                \n➠ Ideal for: Picnic
                \n➠ Opening hours: 1 pm to 8 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutPraduman">➠ Located near Lalpari lake in Rajkot, this park is one of the famous places 
                in Rajkot. The park is spread across an area of 137 acres and offers many species 
                of animals and plants. If you are visiting Rajkot with your family, then you must 
                visit this place for a soul-satisfying experience.
                \n\n➠ Location: Pradhyuman Park, Rajkot, Gujarat 360003
                \n➠ Entry Fees: INR 10 for adults, INR 5 for children
                \n➠ Ideal for: Family outing
                \n➠ Opening hours: 9 am to 6 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutLalPari">➠ A few kilometres from Rajkot city is Lal Pari Lake, another picturesque
                locale that’s one of the most terrific picnic spots in Gujarat. It’s among the more
                popular tourist places near Rajkot as like Aji Dam, it attracts various migratory
                birds who put on quite a show.
                \n\n➠ Location: Navagam, Rajkot, Gujarat 360003
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Leisure
                \n➠ Opening Hours: 9 am to 6 pm
    </string>

    <string name="aboutNyari">➠ When you want to take a break from museums, we recommend heading to Nyari Dam,
                a scenic Rajkot place to visit that’s perfect for a picnic. It’s located five
                kilometres from Rajkot and although frequented by tourists and locals, it still
                retains a peaceful ambience. The views are lovely and if you stay till evening you
                can catch a beautiful sunset. It is one of the most romantic tourist places in Rajkot
                for couples. In fact, you can find one of the best hotels in Gujarat here.
                \n\n➠ Location: Nyari Dam Rd, Rajkot, Gujarat  360005
                \n➠ Entry Fees: Free
                \n➠ Ideal for: Leisure
                \n➠ Opening Hours: 24 hours
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of BestFood-->
    <string name="aboutGathiya">➠ Ganthiya is a special dish of Gujarat. It makes the best combination
        with sweet chutney and chilly. It is the best side dish with tea or coffee during breakfast
        or snack time. It is delicious and healthy.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutDabeli">➠ Dabeli is the most loved snack item of all the people all over 
        the country. Dabeli marks its origin from Gujarat. It is a delicacy which is like Vada pav 
        of Maharashtra, but the main difference is that instead of Vada, they put mashed potato, 
        groundnut, spices, pomegranates, dates, and tamarind. It is tasty and healthy too.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutGhu">➠ Ghughra is a sweet dish from Gujarat which is loved by all 
        the Gujarati’s. People make this dish during festivals and other occasions. It has some
        sweet stuffing coated with the dough. It is cut in the shape of half moon and is baked. 
        It is delicious and healthy too.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutDal">➠ Dal Pakwan is one of the most famous Sindhi breakfast recipe. 
        Dal pakwan is basically chana dal served with pakwan (crisp fried Indian bread).
    </string>

    <string name="aboutBhungada">➠ Bhungara Bateta  is a mad street food of Rajkot.
        It is spicy with red gravy. Additionally, it contains a mild sweet flavour.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Hostel-->
    <string name="aboutBoysHostel">There are three hostel buildings for boys.
        \n\nThe hostels are well maintained. The hostel building is having construction and
        maintenance in order to accommodate more people and provide new facilities. We have 3 seater
        rooms with attached washrooms, washing machines on each floor, badminton court, table tennis.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutGirlsHostel">There are five hostel buildings for girls.
        \n\nHostels are good. One table is provided in room. One bed is also provided.
        Two shelfs are provided for putting some books. One almira is also provided.
    </string>
    <string name="hostelRules">➠ A student must abide by the Hostel Policy, Rules and Code od Conduct at the
                time of admission to the hostel.\n\n
                ➠ Room allocation is done by the warden based on the choice of the student or/end
                availability in 04/06/07 sharing rooms.\n\n
                ➠ Transfer of room is to be done with official process and authorized by the worden based
                on availability\n\n
                ➠ All the furniture will be provided by the hostel in-charge. The student will incur if any
                item is found damaged or missing from their room due to careless/negligent handling.\n\n
                ➠ Electric appliances shall not be permitted in the room, defiance of which shall enable
                the worden/Campus Administrator to confiscate the gadget forthwith (e.g. iron, induction stove.)\n\n
                ➠ Campus administration like warden/security may come and check your room at any time.\n\n
                ➠ Vehicles are not allowed inside the hostel premises for the hosteler. If student want
                to keep the vehicle, need to park at general parking area which is outside of the campus.\n\n
                ➠ Hostel authorities can terminate the occupancy in case of willful disobedience or
                defiance of authority . non - observance of hostel rules , causing damage to person
                or property or anti - social , anti - national or undesirable activities as Ragging ,
                Gambling , Alcohol / Drugs / Smoking , Misuse of Internet and Online social media ,
                Firearms , Pets , cooking inside the room , political and communal activities etc.\n\n
                ➠ During the vacation student need to keep all the things into the locker.\n\n
                ➠ Students need to mark his / her signature on the attendance muster between
                08:00 pm to 9:30 pm ( Based on the allocated time by warden ) in the presence of warden.\n\n
                ➠ Student can go outside with permission of warden ( Gate Pass ) once in a week.
                In such case student need to return at campus on or before 07:00 pm.\n\n
                ➠ The student is permitted to go outstation for participating in various competitions
                only after submitting proof and application along with parent\'s consent to the
                warden and getting permission of the warden.\n\n
                ➠ Students need to return from outstation before 09:00 pm ( Based on the given
                time by warden ) , after which gates will be closed . ( In case of late arrival ,
                student need to inform to warden and take prior permission ).\n\n
                ➠ Visitors / Parents are allowed to visit a student only in the visitor\'s lobby on
                the service floor between 9:00 am to 6:00 pm . Parents are not allowed to visit room.\n\n
                ➠ Strict silence shall be observed in hostel from 12.00 midnight to 6.00 pm.
                Care shall be always taken to ensure that music / loud talking is not audible
                outside the room . Any manner of festivities and noise making / celebrations ,
                which may cause disturbance to other inmates in the hostel premises , will not
                be allowed.\n\n
                ➠ Strict silence shall be observed in hostel from 12.00 midnight to 6.00 pm.
                Care shall be always taken to ensure that music / loud talking is not audible
                outside the room . Any manner of festivities and noise making / celebrations ,
                which may cause disturbance to other inmates in the hostel premises , will
                not be allowed.\n\n
                ➠ The student shall keep their rooms , veranda , and surrounding areas tidy ,
                neat , and clean always and shall not throw anything including trash , in such
                places or any premises in the hostel , except in the dustbin or the place
                specifically provided for the said purpose.\n\n
                ➠ The student shall always treat the hostel staff , security , and housekeeping
                staff of the hostel with due courtesy . Service of the housekeeping staff shall
                not be utilized for private or personal work . No tips in cash or kind should
                be given to the staff of the hostel.\n\n
                ➠ In case of medical emergency , student should contact to warden.\n\n
                ➠ All the rights are reserved by the management.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Details Of Other Activity-->
    <string name="aboutLibrary">➠ There are so many libraries like : Engineering Library, Pharmacy Library,
                Ayurvedic Library, Management Library, Physiotherapy Library, Science Library.\n\n
                ➠  All books are available in the library.\n\n
                ➠ Student can issue any book from their library account for limited time duration.\n\n
                ➠ WI-FI facility also available in all libraries.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutSports">➠ State-of-the-art gymnasium, Sports building, fully-equipped with the
                latest equipment within the campus.\n\n
                ➠ Instructors and trainers are also available to train the students and staff.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutCanteen">➠ The students who come from faraway places, start their journey to
                the College early in the morning. The mid-day meal is provided.
                Even many day-scholars use canteen facilities for their breakfast and evening
                tea with snacks.\n\n
                ➠ Only one common eating facility (canteen facility) shall be provided in the campus for
                day scholars, hostellers, guests of the College, teaching and non-teaching staff of the College.
                The management is fully committed to keeping the quality of the canteen for the utmost
                benefit of all concerned.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Disclaimer-->
    <string name="disclaimer">➠ Personal Details Collected will not be shared with third party and we
        will try to keep your data confidential.
        \n\n➠ Fees for tourist spots mentioned in app are subject to change, Kindly check the
        updated fees with tourist center directly.
        \n\n➠ Admission relative information, select Talk To Us ( Strict action will be taken on prank callers ).
        \n\n➠ If any feedback suggestion related to app contact RKU, ITs.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Journey-->
    <string name="journey">➠ RK University is located in the city called Rajkot in Gujarat state.
        Rajkot is having a domestic airport with flights from Delhi, Mumbai, and Bengaluru.
        Ahmedabad Airport is one of the biggest airports in the Gujarat state which is 228 KM
        far away from Rajkot which takes approximately 5 hours by road.
        \n\n➠ Kindly find convenient airports below if you are coming from foreign countries.
    </string>

    <string name="prem_vadhavana">Prem Vadhavana</string>
    <string name="degree_c_e">Degree : C.E.</string>
    <string name="_21soece13078">21SOECE13078</string>
    <string name="pvadhavana117_rku_ac_in">pvadhavana117@rku.ac.in</string>
    <string name="tulsi_chhatriwala">Tulsi Chhatriwala</string>
    <string name="degree_i_t">Degree : I.T.</string>
    <string name="_21soeit13003">21SOEIT13003</string>
    <string name="tchhatriwala507_rku_ac_in">tchhatriwala507@rku.ac.in</string>
    <string name="naman_thakar">Naman Thakar</string>
    <string name="_21soeit13020">21SOEIT13020</string>
    <string name="nthakar715_rku_ac_in">nthakar715@rku.ac.in</string>
    <string name="darshit_chauhan">Darshit Chauhan</string>
    <string name="_21soeit13002">21SOEIT13002</string>
    <string name="dchauhan069_rku_ac_in">dchauhan069@rku.ac.in</string>
    <string name="ayurvedic_college_and_hospital">AYURVEDIC COLLEGE AND HOSPITAL</string>
    <string name="courses">COURSES</string>
    <string name="place_to_visit">Place To Visit</string>
    <string name="famous_food">Famous Food</string>
    <string name="academics">Academics</string>
    <string name="hostel">Hostel</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="phrase">Phrase</string>
    <string name="reach">Journey To RKU</string>
    <string name="talk">Talk To Us</string>
    <string name="boys_hostel">Boys Hostel</string>
    <string name="girls_hostel">Girls Hostel</string>
    <string name="about_library">ABOUT LIBRARY</string>
    <string name="about_sports_and_gym">ABOUT SPORTS AND GYM</string>
    <string name="about_canteen">ABOUT CANTEEN</string>
    <string name="enter_the_otp">Enter the OTP</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="verify_otp">Verify OTP</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_physiotherapy">ABOUT SCHOOL OF PHYSIOTHERAPY</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_agriculture_science">ABOUT SCHOOL OF AGRICULTURE SCIENCE</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="please_login_in_your_account">Please Login in your account</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget Password?</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="sign_in_with_google">Sign In With Google</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_engineering">ABOUT SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_management">ABOUT SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_pharmacy">ABOUT SCHOOL OF PHARMACY</string>
    <string name="about_school_of_science">ABOUT SCHOOL OF SCIENCE</string>
    <string name="rku_guide">RKU Guide</string>
    <string name="dalpakwan">Dalpakwan</string>
    <string name="ghughara">Ghughara</string>
    <string name="bhungada_bataka">Bhungada Bataka</string>
    <string name="dabeli">Dabeli</string>
    <string name="gathiya">Gathiya</string>
    <string name="analgadh_hill">Analgadh Hill</string>
    <string name="ishwariya_park">Ishwariya Park</string>
    <string name="pradhyuman_zoological_park">Pradhyuman Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="lal_pari_lake">Lal Pari Lake</string>
    <string name="nyari_dam">Nyari Dam</string>
    <string name="about_boys_hostel">ABOUT BOYS HOSTEL</string>
    <string name="rules_and_regulation">RULES AND REGULATION</string>
    <string name="about_girls_hostel">ABOUT GIRLS HOSTEL</string>

    <string name="how_are_you">How Are You?</string>
    <string name="how_are_you1">તમે કેમ છો?</string>
    <string name="what_are_you_doing_here">What Are You Doing Here?</string>
    <string name="what_are_you_doing_here1">તમે અહીં શું કરી રહ્યા છો?</string>
    <string name="can_you_help_me">Can You Help Me?</string>
    <string name="can_you_help_me1">તમે મને મદદ કરી શકો છો?</string>
    <string name="where_do_you_come_from">Where Do You Come From?</string>
    <string name="where_do_you_come_from1">તમે ક્યાંથી આવો છો?</string>
    <string name="did_you_eat">Did You Done Your Food?</string>
    <string name="did_you_eat1">શું તમે જમી લીધું?</string>
    <string name="what_do_you_like_more">What Do You Like More?</string>
    <string name="what_do_you_like_more1">તમને વધુ શું ગમે છે?</string>
    <string name="help_me_to_go_to_mess">Help Me To Go To Mess.</string>
    <string name="help_me_to_go_to_mess1">મેસમાં જવા માટે મને મદદ કરો.</string>
    <string name="help_me_to_go_to_canteen">Help Me To Go To Canteen.</string>
    <string name="help_me_to_go_to_canteen1">કેન્ટીનમાં જવા માટે મને મદદ કરો.</string>
    <string name="which_subject_do_you_like_more">Which Subject Do You Like More?</string>
    <string name="which_subject_do_you_like_more1">તમને કયો વિષય વધુ ગમે છે?</string>
    <string name="which_department_are_you_in">Which Department Are You In?</string>
    <string name="which_department_are_you_in1">તમે કયા વિભાગમાં છો?</string>
    <string name="what_to_do_to_get_to_the_airport">What To Do To Get To The Airport?</string>
    <string name="what_to_do_to_get_to_the_airport1">એરપોર્ટ પર જવા માટે શું કરવું?</string>
    <string name="give_me_your_number">Give Me Your Number.</string>
    <string name="give_me_your_number1">તમારો નંબર આપો.</string>
    <string name="please_contact_me_when_you_come_to_my_country">Please Contact Me \nWhen You Come To My Country</string>
    <string name="please_contact_me_when_you_come_to_my_country1">જ્યારે તમે મારા દેશમાં આવો ત્યારે \nકૃપા કરીને મારો સંપર્ક કરજો.</string>
    <string name="what_is_the_famous_place_here">What Is The Famous Place Here?</string>
    <string name="what_is_the_famous_place_here1">અહીંનું પ્રખ્યાત સ્થળ કયું છે?</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_name">What Is Your Name?</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_name1">તમારું નામ શું છે?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_txt">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="back_to">Back To</string>
    <string name="via_bus">Via Bus</string>
    <string name="via_train">Via Train</string>
    <string name="via_airplane">Via Airplane</string>
    <string name="book_now">Book Now</string>
    <string name="note">NOTE : We will redirect you to another page for booking</string>

</resources>